mymangosteen.com 2005-12-16

# MyMangosteen Privacy Policy

##   
Does MyMangosteen Share My Information With Outside Parties?

Absolutely not. All members and interested parties of MyMangosteen can rest assured that their information will not be sold or rented to any third parties. Personal information, such as billing or shipping, is kept on our secure servers.

You will have access to your Powerline information, which includes the name, city, and order amount of your MyMangosteen organization. Members are only allowed to contact other MyMangosteen members in their line for support or training purposes and cannot share information with others.

## What information Does MyMangosteen.com Collect?

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, tracking your orders and Powerline, sending commission checks, improving our site, and communicating with you.

When ordering products and/or registering on the site, we need you to provide certain information in order for us to create a user profile so that we may customize preferences for each specific user, as well as provide a faster method for users to submit information to MyMangosteen.com, LLC., and receive back either the information or products desired.

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses MyMangosteen.com or any of the other MyMangosteen.com sites. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. If you use one of these products we will not be able to provide a personalized experience at MyMangosteen.com.

## Cookies

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a Web site can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. Cookies allow Web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor's individual preferences. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major Web sites use them. Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent or notify you whenever you are sent a cookie. This gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access most of the features on the site. MyMangosteen.com uses cookies so that they can help provide its visitors with a better experience on our site.

## Security of Personal Information

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission of sensitive/credit data by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. User personal data is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems.

## What Information can I access?

MyMangosteen.com gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list may change as our Web site evolves. 

  * Account Information
  * Public Profile
  * Newsletter Subscriptions

## Kids under 13 (Special Note to Parents)

Pursuant to the provisions of the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect information from children under thirteen years of age without the consent of a parent legal guardian. Parent (or legal guardians) may provide us with consent to collect such information by e-mail, by facsimile or by posted mail. Parents may request to review information collected from their child, may ask to have that information deleted, and may refuse to allow further collection or use of the child's information. To request such review or to give instructions regarding the information we have collected about a child, parents/legal guardians should contact us.

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children, to participate in the interactive activities offered online, and for children to consult with their parents before submitting any information to this or any other web site. Although guest under eighteen years of age may be allowed, with their parent's permission and supervision, to participate in noted contests, if such a guest wins, notification and prizes will be sent to such guest's parents or guardian. Parents should consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help supervise their children's online activities. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other personal information online without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please consult the "Consumer Assistance" page of the Direct Marketing Association home page.

## Does MyMangosteen.com Share the Information It receives?

MyMangosteen.com's Privacy Policy (as detailed below) outlines that we do not collect personal information about individuals except when knowingly provided by such individuals (or as otherwise detailed below). Any personal information (e.g., name, e-mail address, etc.) provided by such individuals may be used in connection with MyMangosteen.com websites and for such other purposes as may be indicated at the point of collection (or otherwise detailed in the MyMangosteen.com, LLC Privacy Policy).

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) on the MyMangosteen.com websites, such information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages.

## What Choices do I have?

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of certain site features.

You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "What Information Can I Access?" section above.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

## Third Party Links

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, MyMangosteen.com may choose various third party Web sites to link to from its own site. However, even if the third party is affiliated with MyMangosteen.com, MyMangosteen.com has no control over these linked sites who each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of MyMangosteen.com. MyMangosteen.com has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, MyMangosteen.com seeks to protect the integrity of its Web site and the links placed upon it and therefore requests any feedback on not only its own site, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work).

## Consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by MyMangosteen.com as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## Contact

MyMangosteen.com welcomes your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to this, or any other issue, at service(at)MyMangosteen.com.
